Guide to the Richard C. Levin Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Teaching files, 1966-1992; Series IV
  - Economics 130a, Economic History, 1969-1971 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Economics 150
    - Examinations, 1976-1978 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Reading list, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Readings, 1979 spring (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Economics 453b
    - General
      - 1990 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - 1991 spring (Box 34, Folder 1-2)
      - 1992 spring (Box 34, Folder 3-4)
    - Class notes, Undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Course readings
      - 1991 spring (Box 34, Folder 6-7)
      - 1992 spring (Box 34, Folder 8-9)
    - Economics 454, Topics in Industrial Organization
      - Antitrust
        - General, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 1)
        - Course description and outline, 1981 spring (Box 35, Folder 2)
        - Reading list, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Competitiveness
        - General, 1988-1989, undated (Box 35, Folder 4-5)
        - Readings, 1988 spring (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Economics 458a, Markets and Governments, 1990 fall (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Economics 520a, Advanced Microeconomic Theory I, 1991 fall (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Economics 600
    - General, 1981-1991 (Box 35, Folder 9-11)
    - Class notes, 1974-1989 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Duplicate lecture notes, 1981-1982 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Reading lists/essays, 1989-1991 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Readings, 1983-1988, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Economics 601
    - General, 1985-1988, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 4-6)
    - Lecture notes, 1986 spring (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Railroad lecture, 1979-1989 (Box 36, Folder 8-9)
    - Reading lists, 1988-1991 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Readings, 1977-1986, undated (Box 36, Folder 11-12)
  - Economics 606a/607b, Dissertation Workshop in Applied Micoreconomics, 1982-1984 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Economics 610b, Economics of Technical Change, 1981 spring (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Economics 785, History of Economic Thought - lecture notes, 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - PPM 150, Economic Analysis
    - Examinations, 1980-1986 (Box 37, Folder 4-6)
    - Examinations and exercises, 1977-1983 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Grades, 1982-1986 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Handouts, 1983 spring, 1986 spring (Box 37, Folder 9-10)
    - Lectures, Undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous teaching material, 1966-1980 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Notes, 1981-1986, undated (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
    - Problem sets, 1981-1986 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Readings, 1983 spring (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Review notes and reading packets, 1986 spring (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - PPM 252b, Regulation, 1982-1984 (Box 39, Folder 1-2)
- Writings, 1976-1990; Series V
  Series V includes drafts of papers for publication in academic journals and related data and notes. There is also correspondence between Levin and journals to which he submitted papers, which include responses to referee reports.
  - Allocation paper correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - American Economic Association deregulation paper, notes, 1980, undated (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - American Enterprise Institute (AEI), abstract of Bell Journal of Economics (BJE) article, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Bell Journal of Economics (BJE) article
    - Boyer comment, 1977-1978 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence on incorrect criticism, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Brookings master copy, 1987 November 25 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Brookings microeconomics panel paper, 1989 December-1990 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Deregulation paper correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Handbook of Industrial Organization (IO)
    - General, 1985-1987 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Chapter, 1987-1988 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Klevorick-Levin
    - Draft, 1982-1983 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Notes, 1983-1984, undated (Box 40, Folder 12-13)
  - Levin-Reiss
    - Data, 1981-1982 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Data and notes, 1983 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Drafts, 1986-1989 (Box 41, Folder 3-4)
    - Programs, 1986-1988 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Levin-Wright survey article, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Oil paper
    - Comments, 1979-1980 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Journal of Economic Behavior and Organization (JEBO), 1980-1981 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Revisions, 1980 August (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Rail merger study, correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - "Survey Research on R&D Appropriability and Technological Opportunity, Part I: Appropriability", 1984 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Computer files (Reel 43)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.